http://www.analyticsystems.com/support/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Analytic Systems
Skip to content
call us 1.800.668.3884
Product SelectorRequest For QuoteSupportShipping & PaymentWarrantiesWarranty RegistrationReturn + RepairCustomer FeedbackDownloadsSearchContact
Search for:
Product LinesProduct SelectorBattery ChargersVoltage ConvertersInvertersPower SuppliesFrequency ConvertersRackmount ModelsOther Products & AccessoriesPart Number & OptionsServicesCapabilities & FacilitiesCustom Design & ManufacturingLean ManufacturingMarketsMarineMilitaryIndustrialTelecommunicationsTransportationAlternative EnergyOur CompanyAboutManagementStatementsCertificationsTestimonialsRelated CompaniesCareersCompany NewsTrade Shows & ConferencesPress ReleasesMediaContact
Search for:
Product LinesProduct SelectorBattery ChargersVoltage ConvertersInvertersPower SuppliesFrequency ConvertersRackmount ModelsOther Products & AccessoriesPart Number & OptionsServicesCapabilities & FacilitiesCustom Design & ManufacturingLean ManufacturingMarketsMarineMilitaryIndustrialTelecommunicationsTransportationAlternative EnergyOur CompanyAboutManagementStatementsCertificationsTestimonialsRelated CompaniesCareersCompany NewsTrade Shows & ConferencesPress ReleasesMediaContact
Search for:
Privacy PolicyAnalytic Systems2018-02-27T22:49:29+00:00
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting analyticsystems.com, we appreciate your visit. We know privacy is important to you, and want you to be comfortable as you explore our site, and share in the interactive nature of the site. We do not share personally identifiable information collected at this site with third parties. Below is a summary of our site information practices. Please note, the privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy are for this Web site only.
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy and is subject to change without notice. Any changes made to this policy will be posted.
Personal Information UseWe do collect personal information, like names, addresses, email addresses, etc., only when it is voluntarily submitted by our online browsers. The personal information you provide us is used to fulfill your request. Meaning, to respond to your request for a proposal, to respond to questions if you have emailed us, and unless you have opted-out, to potentially receive Analytic Systems services and/or special promotional information via email or postal mail. Note, if you provide your name and street address via email from the contact us section or the request for proposal, you will be added to the ASW mailing list. Once on this mailing list, you may receive (by regular mail or email) information occasionally about a variety of ASW services, events, and offers which may interest you.
Your information is kept secure. Only authorized Analytic Systems employees have access to stored information. If you no longer want to receive information from ASW, and you have given us your name and address via the contact us section, you may contact us at 1-800-668-3884 or send us a new email from the contact us section. Please let us know how we initially received your information. Whenever you receive an email from this site, you will also be given the opportunity to opt out of future mailings.GeneralThird party Internet sites accessible through hyperlinks from this site have their own privacy practices, and ASW has no responsibility or liability for these independent practices. Please review their privacy practices for yourself.
SupportShipping & Payment
Warranties
Warranty Registration
Return + Repair
Customer Feedback
Downloads
Copyright & Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
©2019 Analytic Systems Ware (1993) Ltd.   All Rights Reserved.   |
